Guide to the Stanford University, Humanities Honors Program, Theses
Stanford University. Libraries.
- Theses, Accession ARCH-1992-165
  - Butler, Heather L., Perceval's Education in Chretien de troye's Perceval ou le Roman du Graal., 1991 (Box 2)
  - Butler, Lindsay, Erich Auerbach, Milan Kundera and Jean-Paul Sartre on the Validity of Prefiguration. (Box 2)
  - Canty, Sheila A., National Healh Insurance: Past, Present and Future., 1980 (Box 2)
  - Chism, Brent Erik, Representations of gender in Disney's full-length animated films., May 15, 1991 (Box 2)
  - Churchill, Bruce, John Steinbeck as a California writer., May 1979 (Box 2)
  - Crary, Mary Laura, Origins of an American Institution: The Philadelphis Prison 1787-1799. (Box 2)
  - Crawford, Susan Cheryl, The Search for order and individual freedom in American communitarianism and communalism., 1979 (Box 2)
  - Criswell, Brandyn, Solutions: the architecture of E. Fay Jones., 1990 (Box 2)
  - Crowley, Jim, Lectio et meditatio: a spiritual reading of the vercelli book., May 1991 (Box 2)
  - Deliganis, Anna, Toward an androgynous aesthetic: language and painting in Virginia Woolf's To the Lighthouse., May 1990 (Box 3)
  - Delio, Philip R., Parables of perversity in the short stories of Fyodor Dostoevsky., May 1991 (Box 3)
  - DeMarchi, Virginia K., Telling Tales: Kafka's Aufhebung of the German fairy tale., May 1990 (Box 3)
  - Deverell, William Francis, Jr., Of chief and other factors: Great Britain and the surrender of Oregon in 1846., May 1983 (Box 3)
  - Ellis, Anne Marjorie, Discourse, policy, and advocacy concerning deaf education in the United States in the mid-nineteenth century: A case study., May 1990 (Box 3)
  - Eno, Robert P., "Weakest Link": the Loyalty-Security case of Physicist Edward U. Condon., May 1989 (Box 3)
  - Estill, Adrianne, Towards reconcilciation: ideology versus subjectivity in Brecht's and Neruda's poetry., May 1991 (Box 3)
  - Fandell, Sarah E., Women of Independent means; powerful women in Shakespeare and Elizabethan and Jacobean England., May 1990 (Box 3)
  - Farnham, Anne, The politics of recovery: Politicization amongst Vietnam Veterans., June 1987 (Box 3)
  - Feldman, Joseph, The tools of rhetoric: Nietzsche's strategies of style., May 1991 (Box 4)
  - Follett, Jeffrey, "Let us seek the true commonwealth": thought and policy in the journal of United labor., June 1989 (Box 4)
  - Fuchs, Alexandra, Cities and souls in the Merchant of Venice., May 17, 1991 (Box 4)
  - Georgiev, Mark L., A sublime moment; representation in the Gesamkunstwerk., May 15, 1991 (Box 4)
  - Gilmarthin, Matthew, A tantalizing promise, a protective interdiction, an auto-erotic essay: the conflict between language and self in three poems by Walt Whitman., May 1992 (Box 4)
  - Gross, Katherine, Beyond the woman question., May 1978 (Box 4)
  - Guest, Courtney, Blaise Pascal's Provincial Letters and their contemporary relevance., December 1991 (Box 4)
  - Hallinan, Kathleen M., Ralph Waldo Emerson: Action versus contemplation in the Life of the Intellectual., June 1989 (Box 4)
  - Hart, Brooke A., The mouth of the migrant: open for construction in Salman Rushdie's The Satanic Verses., May 20, 1990 (Box 4)
  - Hartwell, Allison, John Marshall's living constitution., June 1987 (Box 4)
  - Healey, Brendan, Into the woods: white-indian transculturalizatioin int he colonial period., May 1988 (Box 4)
  - Held, Robert, The Closing of a Child's Mind: The Death of the Imagination., June 1990 (Box 4)
  - Holloway, Jonathan S., Defeating desire while endeavoring to be the best: the conflict between professionalism and pure sport, ideology in modern sports., May 1989 (Box 5)
  - Huber, Gernot, Veronica doesn't either: "Heathers" in the context of recent teen film and feminist film theory., September 1991 (Box 5)
  - Huffman, Jennifer I., The right to be let alone: the debate over the constitutional right to privacy and its implications for sexual maters., June 1989 (Box 5)
  - Humphress, Rick Douglas, Justice Harlan dissenting: an interpretation of federal-state relations., May 1985 (Box 5)
  - Huo, Rick, Wang Wei and Keats., June 1990 (Box 5)
  - Hutchins, Christopher M., The return of the repressed., Spring 1990 (Box 5)
  - Jancu, Robert, Said, Foucault, and the "orientalizing" mythic discourse., June 1990 (Box 5)
  - Katz, Marc David, John Hawkes as Playwright--with special attention to The Undertaker., June 1990 (Box 5)
  - Kennedy, Kristin M., Division and unity in Shakespeare and Faulmner: A comparative analysis of Hamlet and The Sound and the Fury., May 1990 (Box 6)
  - Kevorkian, Martin, The divine in Ironweed: Tropological Allegory in William Kennedy's Dante., 1990 (Box 6)
  - Kimball, Pam, Without liberty and justice for some., May 1978 (Box 6)
  - Kirks, John S., Montaigne on death., June 1991 (Box 6)
  - Klosterman, Theresa Ann, Climbing down from the pedestal: a thematic study of the poetry of La Comtessa de Dia., May 1990 (Box 6)
  - Korobkin, Russell, Hidden Agendas: Confederate Motivation for negotiating with the US government. (Box 6)
  - Kreitzer, Beth, A feminist perspective on Martin Luther., July 1990 (Box 6)
  - Lauer, Craig, A striking instance: the influence of authority in Billy Budd., May 1991 (Box 6)
  - Laugharn, Peter A., Teaching in the Peace Corps., May 1982 (Box 7)
  - Lee, Kristen, Between the worlds of marble and chaos: the quest for security in Virginia Woolf's The Waves., May 15, 1991 (Box 7)
  - Lee, Maurice, Vonnegut and the paradox of hope: Hope and despair in the novels of Kurt Vonnegut., May 1990 (Box 7)
  - Lee, Pauline, Stephen Dedalus and Hsun Tzu: Flying by and flying within the nets of society., 1991 (Box 7)
  - Leifer, Amira K., Vision and design in To the Lighthouse: Art, Intimacy, and Life., December 1989 (Box 7)
  - Lewis, Mark, Evaluation of Kant's Critique of Judgment., 1990 (Box 7)
  - Lippmann, Steve, "The last colony?": Class, race, and the history of Washington, D.C.., June 5, 1991 (Box 7)
  - Lucero, Orlando, The birth of the skyscraper: Chicago, 1880-1900, a new frontier in American architecture., April 1980 (Box 7)
  - Maggioncalda, Jeff Nacey, George Lamming's Backward glance: a tool for understanding rap music., December 10, 1991 (Box 7)
  - Maurer, Genevieve L., Women, weight, and reform in the U. S., 1900-1930., May 1991 (Box 8)
  - Mendoza, Jerilyn Lopez, Defining the spectrum: race and ethnic relations among Stanford students., Spring 1990 (Box 8)
  - Meyer, Rachel A., The tension within Kierkegaard's The Sickness Unto Death: The Possibility of Satrean atheistic existentialism within a Kierkegaardian religious framework., May 1990 (Box 8)
  - Moreno, Michele, Certainty and imagination in the New Science by Giambattista Vico: The essence of humanity., June 1991 (Box 8)
  - Nied, G. David, The education of the moral american Henry James' The Ambassadors and The American and Henry Adams' Democracy and The Education of Henry Adams., May 1981 (Box 8)
  - Packard, Warren, The poetics of technology., June 11, 1991 (Box 8)
  - Pak, Sandra, God, Society, Love, and Life: A Durkheimian analysis of suicide in Anna Karenina. (Box 8)
  - Palmer, Deborah K., "Remembering the dimensions of possibility." Breaking the bonds of social structure: Emily Dickenson's Search for the "Divinest Sense"., May 1991 (Box 8)
  - Peterson, Sarah, The power of the imagination in words; Wallace Stevens' public vision., 1989 (Box 8)
  - Pham, Krystle Quynh, Sexual relations and morality: the challenge of social transformation in Naguib Mahfouz's Midaq Alley., June 1990 (Box 8)
  - Pickett, Jeffrey Gustaf, Right-living in Vienna: a comparative study of Ludwig Wittgenstein's and Robert Musil's Language critiques., 1990 (Box 8)
  - Presant, Ivan, "Which is the merchant here and which the Jew?"., June 1991 (Box 8)
  - Rodgers, Johannah, Voices will listen and words will hear: towards an understanding of Paul Celan's Poetics. (Box 9)
  - Rosin, Hanna, The art of conversion: the image of Jews in three sixteenth century plays., 1991 (Box 9)
  - Sage, John Keith, The Ku Klux Klan of the 1980s: Renaissance v. Resistance., May 1983 (Box 9)
  - Sarkisian, Bruce, The Dodgers' Brooklyn., June 1989 (Box 9)
  - Saul, Scott, Homing pidgins: immigrant tongues, immanent bodies in Abraham Cahan's Yekl., 1992 (Box 9)
  - Schmeling, GIna, Gender as Convention in Joyce's "Ulysses"., June 1990 (Box 9)
  - Schwartz, William P., Why the ACLU?: a Study of the Origins of the American Civil Liberties Union., June 1979 (Box 9)
  - Schwitzgebel, Eric, The Value of Tragedy for Nietzsche., 1990 (Box 9)
  - Shaefer, Katherine M., Attitudes About Intermarriage as Reflected in Mainstream and Black Publications, 1949-1989: A Content Analysis., June 10,1990 (Box 10)
  - Sheehy, Maureen A., "What is Home Without a Father?": the Underground World of Polygamous Mormon Women., June, 1984 (Box 10)
  - Sperling, Robert, The Novelistic Paradigm of Vision: Exploring Ambiguity in the Works of Milan Kundera., May 1991 (Box 10)
  - Spudlich, Serena S., Phrenology and Charlotte Bronte: The 'Meanings' of Science in the Narrative of Nineteenth Century Popular Culture., Spring 1991 (Box 10)
  - Staten, Ben L., Love, Marriage, and the Fate of the Novel. A Critical Analysis of John Updike's Early Works., May 1990 (Box 10)
  - Stenn, Sarah Amelia, Working Girls: An Analysis of the Representation of Working Women and Their Choices in Career Woman Films Between 1940-1950., May 1990 (Box 10)
  - Stone, Nancy, "A Raisin in the Sun" and Lorraine Hansberry: Defining the Debate., May 1991 (Box 10)
  - Symeonides, Joe Han, "For, though I am the son of the Revolution, they are my illustrious ancestors!" The Sinitud of Regino Pedroso., June 1990 (Box 10)
  - Teicholz, Leslie, Travels Within and Without: Christopher Isherwood and Berlin., Summer 1989 (Box 10)
  - Teicholz, Nina, The Tinsley Case., June 1987 (Box 10)
  - Thompson, Lisa, "BIA, I'm Not Your Indian Anymore!": The American Indian Movement. 1968-1973., May 17, 1991 (Box 10)
  - Tyndall, William F., Business and the Clean Air Act of 1970: An Analysis of a Revisionist Interpretation of Liberal Reform., 1979 (Box 11)
  - Velick, Cheryl, The Wizard of Oz: An Introduction to History and the Classics., May 1984 (Box 11)
  - Weiner, Mark Stuart, Definitions of the self in early modern advertising: an examination of the "Cosmology" of listerine and Fleischmann's Yeast., June 1989 (Box 11)
  - White, Matthew P., Fishing the void: Richard Brautigan's search for meaning in Trout Fishing in America, A Confederate General from Big Sur, and In Watermelon Sugar., November 1989 (Box 11)
  - Worthington, Mark F., The privilege of War: poetry of American combatants in Vietnam., May 1988 (Box 11)
  - Zidle, Abby, The function of the incredible in Tom Stoppard's Jumpers., May 8, 1991 (Box 11)
- Theses, Accession ACCN-1993-098
  - Abramowicz, Sarah, To make a man: the erotic transgression of textual pursuit in James Joyce's Ulysses and Virginia Woolf's Jacob's Room., June 1992 (Box 1)
  - Breimhorst, Mark Selin, A Disability Interpretation of Shakespeare's Tragic Characters., 1992 (Box 1)
  - Bruger, Jennifer, the Imaginative Life: To the Lighthouse and the Pos-Impressionis Aestheic., 1992 (Box 1)
  - Claymon, Deborah S., Long Day's Journey into Night from script to film., May 1992 (Box 1)
  - Crampton, Alexandra, Talking to ourselves in the midst of Zuni silence: American textual representations of Sha'lak'o., April 1991 (Box 1)
  - Davidson, Samantha J., Order and subversion: "Blood" in The sound and the fury., May 1992 (Box 1)
  - Derryberry, John Reed, Time paradigms temporal aesthetics in Beckett's theatre., June 1992 (Box 1)
  - Dibble, Samuel Craig, Economic and political influences in the architectural patronage of Cosim de' Medici., May 1992 (Box 1)
  - Dowd, David, Pounding out a poetic presence; purposeful association and distance between Ford Maddox Ford and Ezra Pound., 1992 (Box 1)
  - Edoga, Sherifa O., Dancing to the rhythm of their own definitions., June 1992 (Box 2)
  - Feinberg, Melanie, Clash of the disciplines: an analysis of the Snow-Leavis controversy., May 1992 (Box 2)
  - Fisher, Jaimey, Walter Benjamin as cultural exile: contextualizing Benjamin's "The Paris of the Second Empire in Baudelaire"., May 1992 (Box 2)
  - Gerson, Rachel Fay, Bombs, Betrayals and Broken Bonds. War and the tenuous nature of identity in Elizabeth Bwen's The Heat of the Day., May 199 (Box 2)
  - Gillespie, Jill, Lyric poetry: Priority and Power versus beauty and truth. A comparative study of Harold Bloom's Anxiety of Influence and Stefan George's and Rainer Maria Rilke's relationships to Friedrich Holderlin., June 1992 (Box 2)
  - Ginsberg, Holly M., Coming up for air with Margaret Atwood's Surfacing., May 1992 (Box 2)
  - Hines, Scott Richard, Adolf Loos and Frank Lloyd Wright: the ornament of material and architectural form., May 1992 (Box 2)
  - Holmes, Sheila Mari, Echoing Poe: theory, passion, and conflict in translation., May 1992 (Box 2)
  - Hoskins, Kimberly, Christa Wolf's Nachdenken uber Christa T.: atextual analysis of Chapter 11., June 1992 (Box 3)
  - Kaufman, Karen Beth, Lessons of "Holocaust": Approaches to the "Final Solution" on prime time television., May 1992 (Box 3)
  - Klingelhofer, Kristan, Relationships and Identity in The Waves: A Question of Voice., May 1992 (Box 3)
  - O'Neill, Dan, Reading Walt Whitman (and His critics): The rhetor as literalist., June 1992 (Box 3)
  - Ormseth, Nik, No more to build on there: disillusionment and the pursuit of dignity in Hemingway's "The Capital of the World"., May 1992 (Box 3)
  - Pappas, Kristina, In spite of you: Unity and protest in Brazilian song, 1970-76., May 1992 (Box 3)
  - Richardson, Matthew, Platonic cultural relativism in Conrad's Heart of Darkness or A Case against Chinua Acheba., August 1992 (Box 3)
  - Shang, Barbara Y., Truth by Antithesis: Yeats' Use of the Mask.., 1992 (Box 3)
  - Silbey, Jessica, Between Two Men: The Correspondence of Summer 1926. Boris Pasternak, Marina Tsvetaeva, Rainer Maria Rilke. An essay on Space and Time., May 1992 (Box 3)
  - Soto, Michael, Poetry, Performance, Politics: A study of Two Carribean Dub Poets. [includes audio tape]., 1992 (Box 3)
  - Waddell, W. Matthew, Transformation and Agency: Negotiations among personal, family, and cultural identities in Toni Morrison's Song of Solomon and Beloved., May 1992 (Box 4)
  - Walkes, Jon-cecil, The debate over race, racism and racial equality: the modern Negro problem., 1992 (Box 4)
  - Wolf, Lea, Motioning female: reading for women in four dances., May 1992 (Box 4)
  - Yalom, Ben, Adapting Malamud's Naked Nude: issues in the transformation from literature to stage., June 1991 (Box 4)
- Theses, Accession ARCH-1994-148
  - Abromeit, John, Existential Marxism: Fortschritt or Fehltritt?, September 1993 (Box 1)
  - Brown, Nicholas, "Umbuji Wa Mnazi" and the Poetics of Anthropology., 1993 (Box 1)
  - Carlson, Julia Sandstrom, Parenthetical Space: The Female Body in Margaret Atwood's The Handmaid's Tale., 1992 (Box 1)
  - Castleman, Joshua "Tony", Seeds from the Other Worlds: religious Faith and Interpersonal Love in the Brothers Karamazov., 1993 (Box 1)
  - Chan, Ann Cha-Yee, Visions of the Perfected State of Man: A Comparative Study of Zhuangzi and Xunzi., 1993 (Box 1)
  - Chun, Young P., Despair and faith in Kierkegaard and "Waiting for Godot"., April 1993 (Box 1)
  - Ciriello, Jeffrey Angerer, A pain redeemed: the writings of Jack Kerouac as an expression of a modern catholicism., Spring 1993 (Box 1)
  - Danforth, Maura, Do "Women read more truly than men read women"? A reading of cross-gender representation in nineteenth century fiction., May 6, 1993 (Box 1)
  - Dycus, Jamie S., Hans Arp and the practice of withdrawal. (Box 1)
  - Edwards, Robert, The grotesque deformation of modern Spanish society in Valle-Inclan's "Los cuernos de Don Friolera"., May 7, 1993 (Box 1)
  - Frick, Erika Renate, Productions of ambivalence: child abuse and the legal system., April 12, 1993 (Box 1)
  - Goldenberg, David, Pure blague? An analysis of Donald Barthelme's continuing parody of Modern America., Spring 1993 (Box 1)
  - Goloboy, Jennifer Lee, the influence of the historical romance novel on Mark Twain's A Connecticut Yankee in King Arthur's Court., 1993 (Box 2)
  - Gordon, Rebecca M., Diamond mines and elephants; the empire in Edwardian children's literature., September 28, 1992 (Box 2)
  - Gross, Rebekah, Wordworth and Freud: On two models of therapeutic analysis., May 14, 1993 (Box 2)
  - Hecht, David, Worn trails to finned tails: manifestations of 1950s America in "Shane" and "Rio Bravo"., May 1993 (Box 2)
  - Itakura, Hakura, The utility of absolute beauty by Kawabata Yasunari in the attainment of Intersubjectivity., June 1, 1993 (Box 2)
  - Jennings, Jan Milburn, Auden's pastoral; the mindscapes of "Bucolics"., March 29, 1993 (Box 2)
  - Lintz, Edward, A la recherche du desir feminin. Gender transposition in Stendhal, Flaubert, and Proust., May 26, 1993 (Box 2)
  - Mandell, Daniel S., "I, Say I": Authorship of the self in Samuel Beckett's "Molloy". (Box 2)
  - Mockler, Robby, Between dogmatism and cynicism; how meaning is created and subverted in John Fowles's The Magus., 1993 (Box 2)
  - Pena, Karen, Uncertain patriots in the fragrant kingdom of palms: a historical presentation of German-Brazilian documents., June 1993 (Box 3)
  - Rovner, Abby Gail, Amazon dreams: representations of Isthmus Zapotec Women., May 17, 1993 (Box 3)
  - Schantz, Edward, Surrealism in Salvador Dali and Franz Kafka.., December 11, 1992 (Box 3)
  - Schinn-Schroeder, Tracy, Amiri Baraka, Cultural Nationalism, and the Postmodern Situation.., May 5, 1993 (Box 3)
  - Seaman, Francesca R., Death and Desire: Petrarch's Consciousness of Time in the Poetic of Canzoniere.. (Box 3)
  - Wice, Leila, Writing back to "ancestry": struggles with continuity and the autobiography of Mordechai Abraham White., May 1993 (Box 3)
  - Wing, Jessica, The cutting edge of art: the uses of actual violence in contemporary performance art., May 1993 (Box 3)
  - Wong, Kelvin, Cultural Adaptation in Matteo Ricci's "Tienzhu Shiyi"., 1992 (Box 3)
- Theses, Accession ARCH-1995-063
  - Arana, Michael A., Ironic reproductions: Sacvan Bercovitch, the new historicism, and the denial of agency., June 1992 (Box 1)
  - Branch, Michelle Nicole, Black Enrepreneurs: Adopted Paens of the Inner Cities., 1992 (Box 1)
  - Demsky, Lisa, Portrayals of rape in twentieth century American literature., Spring 1992 (Box 1)
  - Donovan, Edward, Living right with the eyes. Nick's search for a true relationship with nature in Ernest Hemingway's "Big Two-Hearted River"., June 1993 (Box 1)
  - Eisenberg, Jonathan, The battle over vista of the Reagan revolution., Spring 1992 (Box 1)
  - Halvorson, Christina E., Environmental Risks: Separate and unequal. Minority Communities and the Locations of Hazardous Waste Landfills and Incinerators in the United States., Spring 1992 (Box 1)
  - Knudsen, Koe, Christian service in the city. Including a case study of Bayshore Christian Ministries' Service to East Palo Alto., June 1993 (Box 1)
  - Kramer, Karen, Alcohol and acquaintance rape: social and legal prejudice against intoxicated victims., Spring 1992 (Box 1)
  - Lassen, Eric J., Stereotypes in the Musical: A study of the portrayal of gender and sexuality in the American Musical theater of the 1960s., Fall 1992 (Box 2)
  - Lee, Jocelyn, Black women in popular culture: stereotypical presentations by white society and black males contrasted with the realism black women create., Spring 1993 (Box 2)
  - Nellor, Lisa Marie, Government and the arts: a precarious alliance. an analysis of the debate of the National Endowment for the Arts., Spring 1992 (Box 2)
  - Phung, Quan L., The Civil Rights Act of 1990: A study of the leadership conference on Civil Rights' influence in legislative campagns to reverse Supreme Court decisions., June 1992 (Box 2)
  - Rees, Amy E., The art and artifice of Hemingway's self-presentations., June 1993 (Box 2)
  - Reeve, Michael Roland, Total quality: here today, here tomorrow. the history, development, and implementation of quality in American industry., Spring 1992 (Box 2)
  - Schnitz, Katy, "The Winds of Freedom Blow": Anti-Communism At Stanford University in the 1950s.., June 1993 (Box 3)
  - Senna, Danzy, Hiding in the Light: Representations of 'Passing' in African-American Fiction 1890 to1930.., 1992 (Box 3)
  - Typermass, David Arthur, "The Injustice of a Poor Education" A Child's Right to Basic Skills., Spring 1992 (Box 3)
  - Urist, Theresa, Keeping Up with Mrs. Jones: Technology, Modernity, and Gender in 1950s Advertising., Spring 1993 (Box 3)
  - Williams, Stephen R., Guerilla culture or.. .How to fight city hall. An examination of Abbie Hoffman., June 1992 (Box 3)
  - Wu, Judy, The politics of nationalism in San Francisco Chinatown: the pro-China movement, 1969-1976., June 1992 (Box 3)
  - Zonana, Katherine, Women's history from the void to the margin. an examination of three high school United States history textbooks., Spring 1993 (Box 3)
- Theses, Accession ARCH-1998-068
  - Bailey, Clark Williams, The Circular Structure of Parody: Zarathustra IV., May 1996 (Box 1)
  - Bazar, Emily Lisa, Narrator as painter: The subjectivity of description, space, and time in Marcel Proust's a la recherche du temps perdu., May 1996 (Box 1)
  - Brambl, Peter Morgan, Kitsch Laments: Commodity Becomes Memento MOri in the Work of Donald Barthelme and Jeff Koons., 1996 (Box 1)
  - Brewer, Alyssa Ann, The Emergence of Order and Meaning in Selected Dynamic Texts of Gertrude Stein., 1996 (Box 1)
  - Brewster, Jesica, Examining the Developing Role of Wo(man)hod withing the Discussion of American Slavery., 1995 (Box 1)
  - Chen, Ruth, Extravagant love poured at God's feet: the making of a worship dancer as prophetic voice in 2th century American dance., March 1996 (Box 1)
  - Davis, Joshua H. T., The value of truth: An Exploration of Absurdity and Death in Apocalypse Now and Heart of Darkness., May 1996 (Box 1)
  - Fang, Sarah Mieko, "Lowrider Magazine": Defining the ns2:roles of women, gang members, and non-chicanos in Chicano Car culture., May 1996 (Box 1)
  - Ferraris, Amy S., Third entities: cultural myths and the grotesque in Fellini's Giulietta degli spiriti., May 1996 (Box 2)
  - Friedlieb, Linda, Examining the lens of the media: an analysis of historical and newsroom oriented factors in newspaper coverage of the deaths at Kent State and Jackson STate in May 1970., May 1995 (Box 2)
  - Glueck, Jennifer Ellen, Morality, Community, and Individualism: Judaism as a model for Eliot's Humanist Religion in Daniel Deronda., May 1996 (Box 2)
  - Hsu, Eric, Crossing to Eden: Robinson Jeffers, Robert Hass, and a poetry of place., March 1996 (Box 2)
  - Ikoku, Alvan, Plantation lullabies: songs of the enduring enslavement of the self., May 1996 (Box 2)
  - Im, Jeannie, Antic dispositions: parodic re-enactment in Marcel Proust's Within a Budding Grove and Samuel Beckett's How It Is., June 1996 (Box 2)
  - Kohn, Lisa, The San Francisco mime troupe in historical context., 1995 (Box 2)
  - Kurtz, Ari, Tort reform or tort deform? The 1995 Products Liability Reform Debate., May 1996 May 1998? (Box 2)
  - Lambert, Rachel, Gertrude Stein transforms language in a long gay book or language transforms Gertrude Stein in a long gay book., May 1996 (Box 2)
  - Lang, Marina, True and ancient properties: Toni Morrison and the community in Tar Baby., May 1996 (Box 2)
  - Lanoff, Julie, The Black Panther Party's free breakfast for children program: Using service as a strategy for social chanbe., May 1996 (Box 3)
  - Lewis, Patricia, Meat art: the aesthetics of flesh., May 1995 (Box 3)
  - McLane, Anita, The dilemma faced by women's colleges: is single-sex education the best way to educate women? (Box 3)